Here are some questions I thought of that I'm interested in.
إليك بعض الأسئلة التي أعتقد .أني مهتم بها
First, how has employment in the US varied over time?
أولاً، كيف تغير معدل التوظيف في الولايات المتحدة بمرور الوقت؟
Of course, you could ask the same question about another country.
بالطبع، يمكنك أن تطرح نفس السؤال .بشأن دولة أخرى
I'm particularly interested in the US, because that's where I live.
وأنا مهتم بشكل خاص بالولايات المتحدة .لأني أعيش بها
But you may have another country you're interested in investigating.
ولكنك قد تكون لديك دولة أخرى .مهتم بدراستها
In the most recent year we have data on, what are the highest and
في العام الأخير الذي لدينا بيانات بشأنه ما مستويات التوظيف الأعلى
lowest employment levels out of all the countries?
والأدنى في جميع الدول؟
Which countries have those employment levels?
أي الدول التي كانت بها تلك المعدلات؟
And where is the US on that spectrum?
وأين موقع الولايات المتحدة في هذه النطاق؟
Of course, I could ask these same questions for
،بالطبع يمكنني أن أطرح نفس الأسئلة
any of the other variables in the data set, as well.
بالنسبة لأي من المتغيرات الأخرى .في مجموعة البيانات أيضًا
I'm also interested in whether there are any consistent trends across countries.
كما أنني مهتم أيضًا بما إذا كانت هناك .أية توجهات متسقة عبر الدول
For example, have there been any global recessions and
على سبيل المثال، هل كان هناك أي حالات ركود عالمي
if so, can I find them in this data?
وإن كانت هناك، فهل يمكنني البحث عنها في هذه البيانات؟
Answering this last question would be a bit complicated and we're not going
قد تكون الإجابة على هذا السؤال الأخير معقدة بعض الشيء
to get into it in this lesson, but we can definitely tackle the others.
ولن نتحقق منها في هذا الدرس، ولكن .يمكننا الإجابة على الأسئلة الأخرى بالتأكيد